[{"Answer": "Elements of both", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-01", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 2, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Is your focus primarily on positive change in the real world or on financial and economic activity?"}, {"Answer": "Holistically across social, economic, ecological, spiritual, cultural, and political domains", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-02", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "How do you measure your impact?"}, {"Answer": "Active participation", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-03", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Are the stakeholders impacted by your work able to negotiate for their own needs and contribute to the health of the whole or are you driven by a desire for action without consideration of those impacted?"}, {"Answer": "Underserved", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-04", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Are your beneficiaries considered underserved in society or are you just finding alternate ways to serve those who are already covered by existing mechanisms?"}, {"Answer": "Direct relationship", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-05", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Do you aim to create a direct relationship between capital providers and beneficiaries or to maximise market efficiencies?"}, {"Answer": "We measure indirect impact", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-06", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Do your impact metrics take into account indirect impact on stakeholders not directly involved in your organisation\u2019s work or are they purely quantitative in scope and only consider direct beneficiaries?"}, {"Answer": "Novel innovation", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-07", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Are you offering genuine, value-adding innovation or are you just adding complexity?"}, {"Answer": "Strong indicators of evident impact", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-08", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 2, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Is there a strong degree of certainty that demonstrable real-world impact has been, is being, or will be delivered?"}, {"Answer": "Multiple forms of capital", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-09", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "How many forms of capital do you consider?"}, {"Answer": "All three", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-10", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Do you consider your impact across operational, direct, and indirect spheres?"}, {"Answer": "Customised approach", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-11", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Do you allow for customisation or seek to standardise for scale?"}, {"Answer": "Mix of metrics", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-12", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 2, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Are your impact indicators and evaluation approaches differentiated according to location or is impact measured and evaluated the same way in every location?"}, {"Answer": "Cross-sectoral collaboration", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-13", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Do you seek to collaborate across all sectors or work within your own?"}, {"Answer": "Co-created", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-14", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Is your impact achieved through co-creation and collaboration or imposed on others in the belief that it's best for everyone?"}, {"Answer": "Diverse and resilient", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-15", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Do you prioritise diversity and resiliency or do you reduce diversity in favour of standardisation and promote a free, unregulated approach?"}, {"Answer": "Both depth and duration", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "1-16", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Impact", "questionText": "Do your impact metrics focus on the depth of outcomes and duration as experienced by stakeholders or on maximum coverage and short-term, surface-level impact?"}, {"Answer": "Some elements of both", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-01", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 2, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Are you a decentralised and distributed organisation that allows all members to be resourced, empowered decision-makers or is there a core team with a clearly defined hierarchy?"}, {"Answer": "It's being considered", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-02", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 2, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your roadmap include a goal to become a more decentralised organisation or do you intend to remain centralised with a defined hierarchy?"}, {"Answer": "Innovative models that meet the needs of all", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-03", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Do your organisation's governance, ownership, and financing models meet the needs of all within the means of the planet or is it driven by obligations for growth and returns?"}, {"Answer": "Equitable distribution to all directly involved in value creation", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-04", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation share the value created with all who created it or do the investors, owners, and founders benefit disproportionately?"}, {"Answer": "Organic spaces supporting organisational resilience of and the emergence of new ideas", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-05", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation create spaces for abundance, resilience, and impact to\nemerge from the interdependent contributions of all stakeholders or does it attempt to plan, curate, and limit the space for emergence?"}, {"Answer": "Seeks to balance power and equity", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-06", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation seek to redistribute power to improve equity among stakeholders or is power still retained by those with greatest resources, access, and/or technological\ncapability?"}, {"Answer": "Strong culture of personal growth and wellbeing", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-07", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation create the conditions for all members to grow and thrive in conjunction with organisational health or does it restrict the\nregenerative capacity of the individual?"}, {"Answer": "All three", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-08", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation simultaneously focus on the following three lines of work: Developing Oneself (Inner Work), Growing the Capability of a Community or Team, Improving the Health and Value of the System?"}, {"Answer": "Engages vertically and horizontally to identify and build mutually beneficial interactions", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-09", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation recognize and respect the complexity of deep interdependence of all stakeholders, including competitors or does it seek to acquire, compete, and control?"}, {"Answer": "Diverse team and active, collaborative community", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-10", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation promote diversity, participation, collaboration, and reciprocity or is it largely homogenous?"}, {"Answer": "Prioritise transparency, community and trust", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-11", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Is your organisation building and strengthening community networks and working in a spirit of high trust and transparency or is there lack of detailed disclosure and a prevalence of hype and rhetoric?"}, {"Answer": "Expansion through collaboration and reinvestment in impact", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-12", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation aim to expand through collaboration and prioritise reinvestment in impact or does it pursue growth at the expense of impact?"}, {"Answer": "Focus on building conditions for evolution", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-13", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation focus on ends-state and the beginning of the regenerative process or just on ends and the designing of an end product?"}, {"Answer": "Focused on transformational change", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-14", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Is your organisation working to transform the established system, trying to make changes from inside the system, or working within the system?"}, {"Answer": "Encourage expression of unique genius", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-15", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation encourage expression of the unique genius of all members in determination of direction and roles or does it dictate direction and roles?"}, {"Answer": "Maintain a dynamic balance", "Name": "Drivyx ESG", "Question": "2-16", "Response": "Drivyx ESG", "Score": 3, "category": "Regenerative Organisation", "questionText": "Does your organisation maintain a dynamic balance between ever-changing environmental conditions and is it alert to feedback loops and tipping points or does it attempt to control its environment and predict the future?"}]